<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Programming on Panda Learns To Code</title>
    <link>/categories/programming/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Programming on Panda Learns To Code</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© This post is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License，please give source if you wish to quote or reproduce.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/programming/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How to set up a local development environment for Data Science</title>
      <link>/post/how-to-set-up-a-local-development-environment-for-data-science/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/how-to-set-up-a-local-development-environment-for-data-science/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In most of the places, I see a lot of blog post regarding the many case studies or implementation of models. But here in this blog post, I am going to talk about some basic stuff. I feel that this topic is quite important and in general, these are the things which are ignored in most of the cases. As a data scientist, we use IDEs all the times. This is important to configure IDEs correct to use gain the full potential of the IDE and the Programming Language. It does not only increases productivity, but at the same, it makes things easier. Here I am going to talk about two IDEs and Jupyter ecosystem.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>System information for better reproducibility</title>
      <link>/post/system-information-for-better-reproducibility/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/system-information-for-better-reproducibility/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;One of the essential aspects of coding is debugging. Reproducibility makes it easy to share a problem. I have personally seen that if we are stuck in a massive problem, making a smaller reproducible version of it helps in many ways. It is not always easy to think about the problem with a higher dimension of complexity, sometimes making it easier helps to understand the issue in a better way.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One decade of R programming</title>
      <link>/post/an-ode-r-one-decade-of-r-programming/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/an-ode-r-one-decade-of-r-programming/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Today R is completing the 20th year of its journey. I am thrilled and excited to share 50% of this journey. I started using R during my early college days. At that time, we used to write C code to solve various numeric problems.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>