<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Panda Learns To Code</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Panda Learns To Code</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© This post is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License，please give source if you wish to quote or reproduce.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>One decade of R programming</title>
      <link>/post/an-ode-r-one-decade-of-r-programming/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/an-ode-r-one-decade-of-r-programming/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Today R is completing the 20th year of its journey. I am thrilled and excited to share 50% of this journey. I started using R during my early college days. At that time, we used to write C code to solve various numeric problems.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automated documentation using pdoc3</title>
      <link>/post/automated-docstring-using-pdoc3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/automated-docstring-using-pdoc3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Documentation of a project is one of the essential aspects in terms of maintainability. Here, in this article, we will cover pdoc3, a python library which can create documentation quickly without any bottleneck. This library is quite useful for creating documentation for backend or middleware in my mind. I find it challenging to use with math symbols in this, but document generation and hosting quite easy. Pdoc is quite easy to use in comparison with Sphinx, which is quite good with LaTeX symbol and other fancy things.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maintain readability of code in time with Wily</title>
      <link>/post/maintain-readability-of-code-in-time-with-wily/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/maintain-readability-of-code-in-time-with-wily/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;maintainability-code-with-wily&#34;&gt;Maintainability code with Wily&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wily is the tool of choice which will compute and maintain a measure of maintainability of a code in time. This can be important to check that a code is readable or not at a time of development. We all know that a piece of code evolves with time. So, this is important to measure the complexity of a code in time. Here we will see how we can set up this tool to calculate complexity of a code. Also, we will see how we can integrate this in the CI pipelines so we can ensure code quality in time.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Record and share terminal session using Terminalizer</title>
      <link>/post/record-and-share-terminal-session-using-terminalizer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/record-and-share-terminal-session-using-terminalizer/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There are great open-source tools are available to record screen. I personally like &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.loom.com/&#34;&gt;loom&lt;/a&gt; and google hangout. All of these are good. But I recently came across Terminalizer to record the terminal session. It is easy to set up and use. Here in this session, I will quickly demo how I use this tool for document creation and sharing.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tutorial: Quick EDA in Python using Pandas Profiling</title>
      <link>/post/tutorial-quick-eda-in-python-using-pandas-profiling/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/tutorial-quick-eda-in-python-using-pandas-profiling/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;EDA is one of the most important part of any data science work. Recently I have came accross a library called pandas profiling which makes it easier and creates a beautiful shareable report. So, here I am sharing some resouces related to  the project which I feel can be useful.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Docker for Data Science</title>
      <link>/post/docker-for-data-science/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/docker-for-data-science/</guid>
      <description>One of the key problem which I have encountered while working in data science domains for couple of years is reproducibility. This is true for any form of research but it has special importance in data science domain especially if you are working with a code which will be consumed by others. If you are dealing with a code which is not reproducible then you can fix it but if your code is used by others there is no one to fix the problem which is not an error in true sense.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Optimized docker images for Data Science With FastAPI</title>
      <link>/post/optimized-docker-images-for-data-science-with-fastapi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/optimized-docker-images-for-data-science-with-fastapi/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Lets build a container based application which is optimized in terms of resources and integrate FastAPI with it. It will help to interact the app to connect to the internet and at the same time we will try to get the bast of data science stack in python. Here is the basic layout which we will try to achieve,&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python type checking using mypy</title>
      <link>/post/python-type-checking-using-mypy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/python-type-checking-using-mypy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;type-checking-in-python&#34;&gt;Type checking in Python&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;python-is-strongly-dynamically-typed-programming-language&#34;&gt;Python is strongly, dynamically typed programming language.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Strong&lt;/strong&gt; typing means that the type of a value doesn&#39;t change in unexpected ways. A string containing only digits doesn&#39;t magically become a number, as may happen in Perl. Every change of type requires an explicit conversion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Dynamic&lt;/strong&gt; typing means that runtime objects (values) have a type, as opposed to static typing where variables have a type.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For details check &lt;a href=&#34;https://stackoverflow.com/questions/11328920/is-python-strongly-typed&#34;&gt;this&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>