<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Documentation on Panda Learns To Code</title>
    <link>/tags/documentation/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Documentation on Panda Learns To Code</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© This post is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License，please give source if you wish to quote or reproduce.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/documentation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Automated documentation using pdoc3</title>
      <link>/post/automated-docstring-using-pdoc3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/automated-docstring-using-pdoc3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Documentation of a project is one of the essential aspects in terms of maintainability. Here, in this article, we will cover pdoc3, a python library which can create documentation quickly without any bottleneck. This library is quite useful for creating documentation for backend or middleware in my mind. I find it challenging to use with math symbols in this, but document generation and hosting quite easy. Pdoc is quite easy to use in comparison with Sphinx, which is quite good with LaTeX symbol and other fancy things.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Record and share terminal session using Terminalizer</title>
      <link>/post/record-and-share-terminal-session-using-terminalizer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/record-and-share-terminal-session-using-terminalizer/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;There are great open-source tools are available to record screen. I personally like &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.loom.com/&#34;&gt;loom&lt;/a&gt; and google hangout. All of these are good. But I recently came across Terminalizer to record the terminal session. It is easy to set up and use. Here in this session, I will quickly demo how I use this tool for document creation and sharing.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>