<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Code Quality on Panda Learns To Code</title>
    <link>/tags/code-quality/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Code Quality on Panda Learns To Code</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>© This post is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License，please give source if you wish to quote or reproduce.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/code-quality/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Log system and libraries information for better reproducibility in Python</title>
      <link>/post/log-system-and-libraries-information-for-better-reproducibility-in-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/log-system-and-libraries-information-for-better-reproducibility-in-python/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;One of the essential aspects of coding is debugging. Reproducibility makes it easy to share a problem. I have personally seen that if we are stuck in a massive problem, making a smaller reproducible version of it helps in many ways. It is not always easy to think about the problem with a higher dimension of complexity, sometimes making it easier helps to understand the issue in a better way.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automated documentation using pdoc3</title>
      <link>/post/automated-docstring-using-pdoc3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/automated-docstring-using-pdoc3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Documentation of a project is one of the essential aspects in terms of maintainability. Here, in this article, we will cover pdoc3, a python library which can create documentation quickly without any bottleneck. This library is quite useful for creating documentation for backend or middleware in my mind. I find it challenging to use with math symbols in this, but document generation and hosting quite easy. Pdoc is quite easy to use in comparison with Sphinx, which is quite good with LaTeX symbol and other fancy things.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maintain readability of code in time with Wily</title>
      <link>/post/maintain-readability-of-code-in-time-with-wily/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/maintain-readability-of-code-in-time-with-wily/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;maintainability-code-with-wily&#34;&gt;Maintainability code with Wily&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wily is the tool of choice which will compute and maintain a measure of maintainability of a code in time. This can be important to check that a code is readable or not at a time of development. We all know that a piece of code evolves with time. So, this is important to measure the complexity of a code in time. Here we will see how we can set up this tool to calculate complexity of a code. Also, we will see how we can integrate this in the CI pipelines so we can ensure code quality in time.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>